喂
Hello.
我爱死我的新工作了
I love my new job!
亲爱的  你在狂吼
Honey,you're screaming.
你说的没错  我就是
You bet your ass I am!
今天第一天上班感觉太棒了
I just had the best first day ever!
那个厨房  比之前的餐厅大两倍
The kitchen? Twice as big as Allessandro's.
噢  太棒了
Oh,that's great.
说到干净  不只是符合卫生局标准
And clean? Not just health departmentclean,
是莫妮卡式的干净
Monicaclean!
酷毙了
Awesome.
噢  还有同事都很好
Oh,and the people are so nice.
有一个男的叫杰弗瑞  他是餐厅领班
There's this one guy,Jeffrey,he's the maitre d'.
钱德勒  你会很喜欢他的
Chandler,you will love him!
毫无疑问  他是我遇过最风趣的男人了
He is without a doubt the funniest guy I have ever met!
《老友记》  第九季 第6集  男保姆
Friends S09E06 The One With The Male Nanny
这样真好  我知道
This is nice.  I know.
你需要两只手才打得开吗
You need both hands for that?
是啊  真得要
Yeah,I kind of do.
嗯  那这样呢
Well,how's this?
瞧瞧你们两个 手握着手
Look at you two holding hands.
是不是开始认真了呢
Is this getting serious?
你们有没有谈过呢
Have you not talked about it yet?
我是不是让你们很不舒服呢
Am I making you uncomfortable?
如果你再高壮一点  就会扁我了吧
If you were bigger you'd hit me.
不好意思  不好意思
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
很明显  现在就讨论那种事
It's obviously way too early for us
对我们而言是太早了
to be having that conversation.
会吗  或许不会  会吗
Is it?  Maybe not. Is it?
当我离婚后
When I got divorced..
我以为很长一段时间内
I didn't think I'd feel this way
我都不会对任何人有这种感觉了
about someone for a really long time.
而且  我也不认为
Then again,I didn't think
会遇到像你这样的人  而且
I'd meet someone like you. And..
这或许太疯狂快速了
This may be crazysoon,
但我希望给你这个
but I want you to have this.
不  这是口香糖
No,not.. That's gum.
噢  五块钱
Oh,five bucks!
我超喜欢这种事发生的  你知道吗
I love it when that happens,you know?
你不知道兜里有钱
You don't know it's there..
我知道  继续挖
I know. Keep digging.
抱歉
Sorry.
是一把钥匙
It's a key.
老实说  我宁可要那五块钱
To be honest,I think I'd prefer the five dollars.
我公寓的钥匙  哇
It's to my apartment.  Wow!
菲比跟麦克  两人关系的一大步
Big step for Phoebe and Mike.
听着  我不希望你觉得
Yeah, look, I don't want you to feel like
你也要给我你的钥匙
you have to give me your key..
就因为...
Just because...
不  我要  感谢上帝
No,I want to.  Thank God.
哇  我本来还在想
Wow. I was starting to think
我应该不会遇到一个人
I'd never meet someone that..
让我想要这样做的
I wanted to do this with.
拿去吧
Here you go.
太酷了 真的是很酷
This is cool.  It really is.
我知道  太惊人了
I know it. It is amazing.
这些小东西可以把门打开
These little things open doors!
我四星期之后才需要回去上班
So I don't go back to work for another four weeks..
但是我们希望我们的保姆可以马上上班
but we would like our nanny to start right away..
让艾玛有时间可以熟悉她
so that Emma could get a chance to know her.
我觉得这样做是很聪明的
I think that's really smart.
我们交接的过程越容易  对她越好
The easier we can make the transition for her the better.
太棒了  很好
That's great. Great.
那你有没有什么问题想问我们呢
So do you have any questions for us?
没有
Not really.
好了  那谢谢你跑这么一趟
All right. Well,thank you so much for coming.
谢谢  很高兴认识你
Thank you.  It was really nice to meet you.
我们会打电话给你  等一下
We will call you.  Oh,you know,wait.
我是有一个问题
I do have one question.
你们会不定期对人做毒品测试吗
Do you guys do random drug testing?
天啊  我们还真的没想过这个
Boy,we hadn't really thought of that.
没关系  但是如果你们要求做
That's cool. But if you do,
我需要你们提前三天告诉我
I'm gonna need three days' notice.
好的  没问题
Okeydokey!
我们永远都找不到保姆了
We're never gonna find a nanny.
别这样  瑞秋
Come on,Rach.
我保证我们会找到的
We will. I promise.
我们还有其他的面试
We have more interviews.
就算糟糕到极点
Worse comes to worst,
我们总是可以重新考虑第一个人选
we can always reconsider the first one we met with.
什么  那个没穿胸罩的金发女郎吗
What,the blond with no bra?
她的头发是金色的吗
She was blond?
等一下
Just a sec.
好的  接下来的应聘者叫桑迪
Okay,this one's name is Sandy.
她有幼儿教育学位
She's got a degree in Early Childhood Education.
她在上个家庭做了三年保姆
She worked for her last family for three years.
嗨  我是桑迪
Hi. I'm Sandy.
而且她看起来有点男性化
And she's a little mannish.
噢  我的天  大卫
Oh,my God! David!
现在会打扰你吗
Is this a bad time?
不  现在很好  进来吧
No,it's a great time! Come in!
天啊  你来这里做什么呢
Oh,my gosh! What are you doing here?
你从明斯克回来了吗
Are you back from Minsk?
只回来几天
Just for a couple of days.
我是回来跟提供基金的人解释
I'm here to explain to the people who gave us our grant..
为什么我们花光了所有他们给的钱
why it's a positive thing that we've spent all their money..
却毫无成果  是件好事
and accomplished nothing.
谁在乎呢  反正你回来了
Who cares? It got you here.
剩的钱足够我买机票飞到纽约
It got me to New York anyway.
然后在机场叫了部计程车
Then I got in a cab at the airport..
司机问我要去哪
and the guy said,"Where to?"
我就给了他你的地址  想都没想
I just gave him your address. I didn't even think about it.
你的行李呢
Where's your luggage?
该死
Damn it.
好了  我来打电话给计程车公司
All right,I'll call the cab company.
等等  我们可以等一下再打
Wait, wait, We can call them later.
你可以先站在那边一会儿吗
Can you just stand there for a moment?
天啊
Boy.
有一句俄罗斯老谚语是这样的
There's an old Russian expression that goes:
大致的翻译就是
Roughly translated,that means:
"我现在盯着的东西  哇"
"This thing that I'm looking at: Wow."
谢谢你
Thank you.
你应该看看当我
You should see me when..
事实上  不用  我看起来挺不错的
Actually,no,I look pretty good.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
你知道的  当很久没有见到一个人
You know,when you don't see someone for a long time..
你会在脑海中建立起这个人的影像
you build them up in your head,
然后开始想
you start thinking:
"少来了  别发神经了
"Come on,don't be crazy,
没人是那样美的"
nobody's that beautiful."
但是  你真就那样美
But,well,you are.
那么  你现在有在跟谁交往吗
Well,so are you seeing anyone?
没有
No.
我是有史以来最糟糕的人
I'm just the worst person ever!
我怎么可以不告诉大卫
How can I not tell David
我跟麦克在一起呢
that I'm seeing Mike?
或许他没有给你机会说
Maybe he didn't give you a chance.
他问我有没有跟谁交往  而我说没有
He said,"Are you seeing someone?" and I said,"No."
本来你是可以趁机告诉他的
Well,that would've been your window.
我也不知道怎么回事  我看着他的双眼
I mean,I don't know. I was looking in his eyes..
然后只能想
and I was just thinking,
"我的天  是大卫  大卫回来了"
"Oh,my God,it's David. David's here."
他真是令人无法抗拒
He's so irresistible.
不是吧  那个科学家
Really? The scientist guy?
不是吧  钱德勒
Really? Chandler?
继续说
Continue.
然后越来越糟糕
Then it gets worse..
因为我答应他  明晚跟他见面
because I told him I would see him tomorrow night.
菲比 我知道  太差劲了
Phoebe!  I know! Evil!
我真的好喜欢麦克
I like Mike so much,you know?
发展得真的很顺利  我的天
It's just going really well. Oh,my God!
真是讽刺  大卫居然出现在
Isn't it ironic that David would show up..
你和麦克交换钥匙的同一天
on the same day that you and Mike exchange keys?
是啊  而且
Yeah. You know,
我一辈子都在找寻讽刺的事
and given my lifelong search for irony..
你可以想像我有多开心
you can imagine how happy I am!
你要怎么办呢  我想我只能
What are you gonna do?  I mean,I guess I just have to..
告诉大卫我们之间是不可能的
tell David that nothing can happen between us.
除非我不告诉他
Unless I don't.
你知道的  复杂的道德情况
You know,complicated moral situation?
没有对错之分
No right,no wrong?
你必须告诉大卫
You have to tell David.
好吧  我就知道我该去问乔伊才对
Ok, I knew I should've had this conversation with Joey.
她遇过的最风趣的男人
Funniest guy she's ever met.
我很风趣  不是吗
I'm funny,right?
你知道个什么  你只是一道门
What do you know? You're a door.
你就像是"敲敲门"的笑话
You just like knockknock jokes.
等到里面再发挥
Save it for inside.
奥克拉荷马真是疯狂
So Oklahoma's a crazy place.
他们把那里称为先锋之州
You know,they call it the Sooner State.
老实说  我宁愿早"先"一点搬到别的州
Frankly,I'd sooner be in any other state!
而且奥克拉荷马为什么有个平底锅柄呢
And what's with Oklahoma having a panhandle?
其它的州可以有像那样的东西吗
Can all states have stuff like that?
嘿  我是从怀俄明州的腰部来的
Hey,yeah,I'm from the waistband of Wyoming.
但是当我7岁的时候
But when I was 7,
我们就搬到胯下部了
we headed over to the crotch.
你坐的机舱是不是压力太大
Was your cabin pressurized?
而且别让我开口吐槽
And don't get me started on the way
塔尔萨人说话的方式
the people from Tulsa talk.
好的
Okay.
"你全"到底是个什么词呢
What's with the word "y'all"?
只不过是"你们"跟"全部"加在一起
You know,just two words just pushed together?
我们可以那样做吗
Are we all allowed to do that?
因为如果可以  还有很多字可以这样玩
Because if so,I say why stop there?
你的"新狮子狗" 可以变成你的"新狮"
You know,your new poodle could be your noodle.
"油炸鸡块"可以变成"炸块"
And fried chicken could be fricken.
服务生  服务生
Waiter? Waiter,
不好意思  我想要点"炸块"
excuse me,I'll have the fricken!
瞧  "炸块"很好笑吧
See,that's funny with the fricken,right?
不  只是让我想起
No,it just reminds me
今天工作时  有个人讲的笑话
of something this guy did today at work.
我有跟你提过
I told you about
一个叫杰弗瑞的风趣的人  对吗
that funny guy,Jeffrey,right?
是啊  你提过
Yeah,he came up.
他说了一件好笑的事
Well,he did this bit.
你应该要在现场才感受的到
You probably had to be there..
说的是莉莎·明妮莉被锁在冰箱里
but it was Liza Minnelli locked in our freezer
吃生鸡肉
eating a raw chicken.
你在现场吗
Were you there?
没有  但听起来"炸"好笑
No,but it sounds fricken funny.
我真的可以理解
I really understand
要把孩子交付给另一个人是很困难的事
how hard it's gotta be to leave your child with another person.
我是说  那就像把心上的一块肉割下
I mean,it's like leaving behind a piece of your heart.
桑迪  你说的对极了
Sandy,that's exactly what it is.
你是同性恋吗
Are you gay?
没关系  我的工作常引来误会
It's okay. I get that a lot doing what I do.
但我不是同性恋  事实上我已经订婚
But I am straight. I'm engaged,actually.
未婚妻名叫狄莉亚  真是好名字
Her name's Delia.  That's pretty.
所以你只是一个当保姆的男人
So you're just,like,a guy who's a nanny.
我知道这对一些人来说是很颠覆传统的
I realize how it's a bit unorthodox for some people.
但我真的相信
But I really believe
人一辈子能做的满足感最强的事
the most satisfying thing you can do with your life..
就是照顾孩子
is take care of a child.
好吧
Okay.
就像我上一任工作
Like at my last job.
我在丹尼尔三星期大的时候就认识他
I met Daniel when he was 3 weeks old.
然后我看着他长大成一个很棒的人
And I got to watch him grow into this awesome person.
当我离开的时候
When I left,
我说  希望很快再见到你
I said,"I'll see you soon."
然后他说  "桑卡爹迪"
And he said to me,"Skadandy?"
那是他给我取的名字
That was his name for me.
"我每天都会看到你在"
"I'll see you every day right in.."
没关系
It's okay.
是啊  小孩子尽会说些鬼话
Yeah,kids say all kinds of crap.
天啊  她一定是需要换尿布了
Oh,God,she must need her diaper changed.
我可以帮你处理  如果你愿意的话
I can take care of that,if you want.
太棒了
That would be great.
我爱他  我爱他  我爱他
I love him,I love him,I love him!
别这样  瑞秋  他是个男人
Come on. Rach,he's a guy!
那又如何  他很聪明  资历又符合
So what? He's smart. He's qualified.
给我一个理由为什么我们不能试用他
Give me one good reason we shouldn't try him out.
因为这实在太奇怪了
Because it's weird!
为什么
Why?
男人做那种工作像话吗  保姆
What kind of a job is that for a man? A nanny?
我是说  那就像一个女人想要成为
I mean,it's like if a woman wanted to be..
什么
Yes?
国王
King?
我希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
我在艾玛身上用了我自制的乳液
I used some of my homemade lotion on Emma.
是混合金盏花跟蜂蜜的乳液
It's a mixture of calendula and honey cream.
对红疹是立即见效的
It'll dry that rash right up.
而且  使双手保持年轻
Plus,it keeps the hands young.
真棒  桑迪  你被录取了
Yes! Sandy,you're hired!
太棒了
That's great!
不好意思
I'm sorry.
只是被欢迎加入一个新家庭
It's just such an emotional thing
是一件很令人感动的事
when you're welcomed into a new family.
噢  天啊  过来这里
Oh,God. Come here.
你至少也是双性恋
You gotta be at least bi.
我需要你搭档讲个笑话
I need you to set me up for a joke.
待会儿等莫妮卡在的时候
later when Monica's around,
你要问我消防车怎样
I need you to ask me about fire trucks.
我不知道  钱德勒
I don't know,Chandler.
我不是很会记台词的
I'm not so good with remembering lines.
感谢上帝  你不是靠记台词吃饭的
Thank God your livelihood doesn't depend on it.
我知道  棒吧
I know,right?
我们为什么要这样做呢
Why are we doing this?
莫妮卡说他们餐厅的领班
Monica says that her maitre d'
是她遇过的最风趣的男人
is the funniest guy she's ever met.
真的吗  她真的那样说
Seriously? She actually said that?
是的  我很愤怒  是不是不对劲
Yes. Am I crazy to be this upset?
不  风趣是你的专利  是啊
No! Being funny's your thing!  Yeah!
没有了它  你还有什么吸引女人的
Without that,you just got "lame with women"!
嗨  你们都在
Hi! There you are.
消防车
Fire trucks!
哇  你看起来比昨天更美丽
Wow. You look even more beautiful than you did yesterday.
事实上  我现在要亲你
In fact,I'm going to kiss you now.
等等  我就是没有办法
Wait,wait.  I can't get away with stuff like that.
在我脑海中听起来很性感  所以我
It sounded sexy in my head,so I..
不  不是那个原因
No,no,it's not that.
你记得当你问我有没有跟谁交往
Remember when you asked me if I was seeing someone
而我告诉你没有吗
and I said no?
事实上我有  他叫做麦克
Well,I am. His name's Mike.
我应该早点告诉你的  不用
I should've told you.  No.
嗯  你该说的
Well,yeah.
我很抱歉  我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
没关系  我可以理解
Well,it's okay. I understand.
那  你跟那个人在一起幸福吗
Well,are you happy with this guy?
我很幸福 该死
I am happy.  Damn it.
我很抱歉  我不是那个意思
I'm sorry. I don't mean that.
我要你过得幸福
I want you to be happy.
但是只能跟我
But only with me.
不  那并不公平
No,that's not fair.
管他的  离开他吧
Who cares. Leave him.
我不是那个意思
I don't mean that.
是的  我是 我很抱歉
Yes,I do. I'm sorry.
我想我应该离开了
I think I should probably go.
但是  大卫  我只想要你知道
But,David,I just want you to know that,you know..
跟你坦白
telling you this
是我做过的最困难的事
is one of the hardest things I've ever had to do.
我也想告诉你
Well,just so you know..
听到此事可不像在过嘉年华
hearing it wasn't exactly a Vladnik carnival,either.
我们至少可以拥抱道别吧
Can we at least hug goodbye?
当然  可以
Of course. Yeah.
你知道的  在脸颊上亲一下
You know,and a kiss on the cheek
应该也不算太不适当
wouldn't be totally inappropriate.
不  不 我是说
No. No.  I mean..
在明斯克  怎样呢
In Minsk?  Yeah?
是在两边各亲两下
It's two on each cheek..
还有一下亲在唇上
and one on the lips.
好吧  如果那是明斯克的习俗
Well,if that's what they do in Minsk.
在纽约  是
In New York,it's..
噢  天啊
Oh,boy.
一切都还好吧
Is everything all right?
噢  是的  很好  很好
Oh,yeah. No,it's fine. It's fine.
桑迪只是在告诉我
Sandy was just telling me
他是如何向他未婚妻求婚的
about how he proposed to his fiancee..
实在是太美了
and it was so beautiful.
她最喜欢的花是山茶花 从那首诗
Her favorite flower is the camellia. From the poem..
我没办法再听一次
I can't hear it again!
我也没办法再说一次
You know,I can't tell it again!
我一遍没听过也挺好的
And I'm fine never having heard it.
瑞秋  我可以跟你谈谈吗
Rach,can I see you for a sec?
好啊  失陪了
Yeah. Excuse me.
你有发现那男人
Do you realize that man
在我们家已经哭过三次了吗
has cried in our apartment three times?
我从搬进来之后也没哭过那么多次
I haven't cried that many times since I moved in!
听着  罗斯  桑迪只不过是很敏感
Look,Ross,Sandy's just sensitive.
仅此而已
That's all.
好了  看吧  那就是个问题
Okay,okay. See,that is the problem.
他太敏感了
He is too sensitive.
太敏感就不能照顾我们的小孩吗
Too sensitive to take care of our baby?
不  我是说  那个男的
No,I mean,that guy..
真是太好吃了
These are amazing!
桑迪做的饼干
Sandy made madeleines.
我想说的正是这个
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
什么样的男人会做精致的法式饼干呢
What kind of a guy makes delicate French cookies?
看起来都不像是男性化
They're not even butch,
雄纠纠的饼干  有那种
manly cookies with..
你知道的  大块咬的快感
You know,with chunks!
你知道的  我不知道能说什么
Well,you know,I don't know what to say.
我是说  我从没想过你是那种
I mean,I never thought of you as a guy
需要"男人"是真正男人的男人
who needed his men to be men.
我必须告诉你  罗斯
I gotta tell you,Ross,
你也不像是脸上有烙印的猛男
it's not like you just came in from branding cattle.
嘿  敏感跟太敏感是有区别的
Hey,there's sensitive and there's too sensitive.
好吧  那什么叫做太敏感呢
Okay,what is too sensitive?
不  我不能
No,I can't.
我不能这样做  这样不好
I can't do this. It's bad.
但是感觉很棒  而很棒就是好
But it's nice. And nice is good.
而好就不是坏事
And good is not bad.
因此  我们应该继续亲吻
Ergo,we should keep kissing.
不  不  不 但是
No,no. No.  But..
因此
Ergo.
听着  大卫  如果你没有离开过
Look,David,if you had never left,then..
那或许现在我们还是在一起的
yeah,we'd probably still be together right now.
但是你离开了
But you did leave.
而我现在跟麦克交往  而且我很在乎他
And I'm with Mike and I really care about him.
再见
Goodbye.
钥匙可以用
The key works.
你  谢谢你的脸部按摩 谢谢你
And,you,thanks for the face massage! Thank you!
瑞秋有告诉你  我们雇了一个男保姆吗
Did Rachel tell you we hired a male nanny?
我认为那太棒了  是吗
I think that's great!  Oh,really?
她有说他会吹直笛  吟诗
Did she tell you he plays the recorder,recites poetry
还会做马德琳饼干吗
and bakes madeleines?
好吃吗
How are they?
清淡爽口  但那不是重点
Lighter than air,but that's not the point.
瑞秋和我雇了一个男保姆
Rachel and I hired a male nanny.
真的吗
Really?
男人会做那样的工作吗
Guys do that?
真是奇怪  谢谢你
That's weird.  Thank you!
那就像是女人想要成为  什么
That's like a woman wanting to be..  What?
成为什么
What's the end of that sentence?
是啊  成为什么
Yes. What is the end of that sentence?
阴茎模特
A penis model!
你告诉钱德勒  你有一个男同事
Anyway,did you tell Chandler that some guy from work..
是你遇过最风趣的男人吗
is the funniest guy you ever met?
有啊  怎样呢  哇
Yeah. So?  Wow!
真的吗  你是不了解钱德勒吗
Really? Do you not know Chandler?
他最近是因此才行为诡异的吗
Is that why he's acting so weird?
他在吃醋吗
He's jealous?
我的天  真是太疯狂了
Oh,my God,that is crazy.
又不是说我喜欢上杰弗瑞 那又怎样
It's not like I'm attracted to Jeffrey.  So what?
风趣是钱德勒的专长
Being funny is Chandler's thing.
就像罗斯的专长就是
Like Ross' thing is..
科学
Science?
学术  做个好父亲
Academia? Being a good father?
不是
No.
我不敢相信他那么生气
I can't believe he's that upset this.
莫妮卡  你要做一些事来弥补
Monica, you have to do some damage control.
因为他觉得
Because he's feeling like..
你们在说些什么
What are you guys talking about?
瑞秋跟我雇了一个男保姆
Rachel and I hired a male nanny.
你雇了一个男人当保姆
You got a man who's a nanny?
你雇了一个"男保"
You got a "manny"?
你知道的  我是不介意男保姆
You know,I don't mind a male nanny..
但我倒是很介意男性乳母
but I do draw the line at male wet nurse.
你真会讲笑话  老兄
You are on a roll,mister!
如果我知道你们要过来
If I'd known you guys were coming over,
我就会多买几份批萨
I would've brought more pizza.
好啦  停止  你  你快停止
Okay! Okay! Stop it,you! You stop it!
那有什么好笑的呢
What is so funny about that?
我不知道  就是  你说的方式很好笑
I don't know,it's.. Just the way you say it.
我是说  你很风趣
I mean,you're funny.
你有风趣的特质  你是很风趣的人
You have that funny thing. You're a funny guy!
你跟她说了我们谈过的事吗
Did you tell her what we talked about?
所以那些是同情的笑声吗  同情笑声
So those were pity laughs? Pity laughs?!
亲爱的  听着
Honey,listen.
你根本不需要担心杰弗瑞
You have nothing to worry about with Jeffrey.
噢  是吗  他比我风趣吗
Oh,yeah? Is he funnier than me?
你们风趣的方式不同
Well,you're different funny.
我是说  你是比较挖苦式的
I mean,you're more sarcastic.
他是做一些模仿跟打油诗等等的
Well,he does bits and impressions and limericks.
我也会打油诗啊
I do limericks.
有一个叫做钱德勒的男人
There once was a man named Chandler
他老婆让他死在里头
whose wife made him die inside.
亲爱的  你知道我认为你超好笑的
Honey,you know I think you're hilarious.
你记得你上星期告诉我的笑话吗
You know that joke you told me last week?
杰瑞·路易斯跟
The one about Jerry Lewis
睡眼惺忪女生的笑话
and the girl with the lazy eye.
那真是笑死我了
That slayed me.
嘿  那是我编出来告诉你的
Hey! I made up that joke and told it to you.
不知道什么时候该闭嘴
Not knowing when to shut up.
是的  那就是我的专长
Yep,that's my thing.
有多少男人有你家的钥匙呢
So how many guys have your key?
不  实际情况并不像看起来这样糟
No, It's not as bad as it looks.
我只是在跟一个老朋友道别
I was saying goodbye to an old friend.
你的口红都在他唇上了
Your lipstick's on his mouth.
我们只是刚好都用相同的口红
We just happen to wear the same shade.
不  我跟大卫以前在一起过
No,David and I did used to go out.
但是是几年前了
But years ago.
而且他住在明斯克
And he lives in Minsk.
他只是回来几天而已
He's only in town for a couple days.
你有没有  没  没有
Did you..?  No. No.
亲他  噢  嗯  有
Kiss him?  Oh,well,yeah.
是的  但是 听着  她真的很喜欢你
Yes,but.. Look,she really likes you.
我觉得你并不知道你有多幸运  老兄
I don't think you realize just how lucky you are,fella.
别用手指指着我  为什么
Don't point your finger at me!  Why?
你要怎样呢
What are you gonna do about it?
好的  我会让你瞧瞧我能怎样
Well,I'll show you what I'm gonna do about it.
你想试试看吗
You want some of that?
噢  真的吗  真的吗
Oh,really? Really?
停止  停止
Stop it! Stop it!
趁没人受伤赶快停止
Before someone gets really hurt!
拿去  大卫  你该离开了
Here,David,you should just go.
好的
All right.
但是如果我从明斯克回来
But if I ever do come back from Minsk,well,
你最好小心一点
you just better watch out.
如果我去明斯克  你也小心点
If I go to Minsk,you better watch out.
噢  你会去明斯克吗
Oh,you're going to Minsk?
噢  或许会  真的吗
Well,I might.  Really?
如果你要去  最好在春天
Well,if you do,come in the spring.
春天是很宜人的
It's just lovely there.
好了  你们
Okay,well,guys?
再见  菲比  再见
Goodbye,Phoebe.  Bye.
嘿  你开什么玩笑
Hey,what,are you kidding me?
对哦  对哦
Righto. Righto.
好好照顾她
Take good care of her.
我很抱歉  非常抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
如果你想拿回你的钥匙  我完全理解
If you want your key back,I totally understand.
这不会再发生了  对不对
It's never gonna happen again,right?
没错  我发誓绝不
Right. Never. I swear.
我只想说
I just want to say,
如果你来明斯克  这是我的号码
if you do ever come to Minsk,that's my number.
我们可以大狂欢起来
We'll party up Vladnikstyle.
真棒  真好
Yeah! All right!
嘿  罗斯  快过来
Hey,Ross! Check it out!
桑迪教我吹《热十字面包》
Sandy taught me "Hot Cross Buns"!
是吗  听起来像是《三只瞎眼鼠》
Really? Sounded like "Three Blind Mice."
不  《三只瞎眼鼠》是这样
No, "Three Blind Mice" goes like this.
别逼我弄死你
I swear to God.
谁想要看布偶秀呢
Who's up for puppets?
我  我要看布偶秀
Me! I'm up for puppets!
噢  请欢迎
Well,please welcome:
鼻塞小子
The Snufflebumps!
谁想要当摇摆先生
Who wants to be Mr. Wigglemunch
还有谁想当小挑剔
and who's gonna be the Grumpus?
够了  够了  一个两岁大的婴儿
Ok, ok, how exactly is a 2monthold
怎么看得懂布偶呢
supposed to appreciate puppets?
事实上  研究显示动作和颜色
Actually studies show that the movement and colors
可以帮助大脑发展
help their cerebral development.
古怪的角色只是要让我们笑而已
The whimsical characters are just for us.
我想要当摇摆先生
I want to be Mr. Wigglemunch!
噢  我的天
Oh,my God.
我想我知道谁要当小挑剔了
Well,I guess we know who's gonna be the Grumpus!
你实在是有点没礼貌
That was kind of rude.
噢  我很抱歉
Oh,I'm sorry.
请代我向桑迪和鼻塞小子道歉
Please apologize to Sandy and the Snufflebumps for me.
你知道的  他只是在做份内的事
You know,he was just doing his job.
你知道吗
You know what?
我很抱歉我是唯一 一个
I'm sorry I'm the only one
不喜欢《魔法保姆》的人
who isn't in love with Gary Poppins out there.
但我只是  我就是没有办法接受
But I just.. I can't go through with this.
别这样  不  你知道吗
Come on.  No! You know what?
很抱歉  但我绝对不会强迫你
I'm sorry, I would never force you
雇用你不喜欢用的人
to hire someone you were this uncomfortable with.
那倒是真的
That's true.
谢谢你
Thank you.
是你要解雇他的  你去跟他说
You want to fire him,so you have to go do it.
所以  摇摆先生
So you see,Wigglemunch,
这就是分享的重要性
that's why it's important to share.
我从你身上学到好多
I am learning so much from you.
好了  我要去塔尔萨了
Well,I'm off to Tulsa.
如果你的领班朋友
So if your maitre d' friend
有任何关于奥克拉荷马的精彩笑话
has any funny Oklahoma jokes..
叫他发电子邮件到
tell him to email me at
www.不怎么好笑.com
wwwdothahanotsomuchdotcom!
亲爱的  你可以放轻松了
Honey,you can relax.
昨晚工作时杰弗瑞说了个
Last night at work Jeffrey told
很性别歧视的笑话
this really sexist joke.
从那之后  其实也不怎么好笑了
After that,not so funny anymore.
真的吗
Really?
瞧  都是这样的
See,that's the thing.
要放聪明一点才行  愚人们
You gotta keep it smart,people!
别错过班机  你知道我爱你
Don't miss that flight. You know I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
而我像朋友一样喜欢你  没错
And I like you as a friend.  Right.
再见  再见
See you later.  See you.
那家伙真的有说那个笑话吗
Did the guy really make that joke?
没有  他还是让我捧腹大笑
No,he still kills me.
我发誓昨晚他让我笑到
Last night he had me laughing so hard,
真的有点尿跑出来
I swear a little pee came out.
你瞧瞧
Here goes.
我不能看
I can't watch.
就像开除艾摩一样
It's like firing Elmo.
桑迪  嗨
Sandy? Hi.
嗨  我们
Hi.  We..
我们可能需要谈谈
We kind of need to talk.
恐怕我们的雇佣关系到此为止了
I'm afraid it's not working out.
我是说  瑞秋跟我都认为
I mean,Rachel and I think
你带艾玛实在是很棒
you are great with Emma.
我们只是觉得  你  只是你觉得
We just feel..  You! You feel!
我只是觉得...
I just feel that the..
没有化学反应  我很抱歉
chemistry isn't right. I'm sorry.
我们很乐意帮你写推荐信的
We're more than happy to give you a good recommendation.
不  没关系
No, no, that's okay.
我挑选你们是因为
I just picked you guys because..
我最喜欢你们
I liked you the best.
噢  该死的  盖勒
Oh,damn you,Geller!
总之  我很高兴没有任何不愉快
Anyway,well I'm glad there's no hard feelings.
不  一点也没有
No, none at all.
你们有权找一个相处融洽的人在家里
You need to be happy with whoever is in your home.
不过  如果你不介意告诉我
Although,if you don't mind telling me..
问题是出在哪里呢
what was the problem?
或许是我将来可以改进的地方
Maybe it's something I can work on in the future.
不  不关你的事  是我的问题
No,you know,it's nothing you did. It's my issue.
是什么呢
What is it?
拜托
Please?
我只不过是不习惯
You know,I'm just not that comfortable with
跟像你一样敏感的男人相处
a guy who's as sensitive as you.
可以谅解
That's fair.
但是  我可以问你为什么会是这样吗
Although,can I ask,why do you think that is?
为什么  我不知道
Why? I don't know.
或许是我父亲的缘故
Maybe because of my father?
在我的成长过程中
You know,when I was growing up,
他总是像个硬汉一样
he was a tough guy.
小时候  我不像现在一样这么有运动感
You know,and as a kid,I wasn't the athlete I am now.
我打壁球的
I play squash!
反正  我总是觉得他认为我太敏感
Anyway,I always got the feeling he thought I was too sensitive.
那一定很难受
That must have been hard.
的确是很难受
It was hard.
我记得有一次我在房间
I remember I was in my bedroom,
跟我的恐龙玩
playing with my dinosaurs..
是一边玩一边学习
Playing and learning.
然后我父亲走了进来说
And my father walks in and says,
他说  你在跟那些东西做什么
he said, "What are you doing with those things?
你有什么毛病
What's wrong with you?
你为什么  为什么不去外面
Why aren't youwhy aren't you outside
像真正的男生一样玩呢
playing like a real boy?"
但你是真正的男生啊
But you are a real boy.
我知道我是的
I know I am!
夏天很热的时候
And when it's summer and it's hot,
为什么不能穿背心装呢
why can't you wear a tank top?!
没关系  哭泣是好事
It's all right. Listen, crying is good.
把委屈都哭出来
It lets the boohoos out.
哭得我停不下来了
Here comes some more!
哪一种船是永远不会沉的呢
And what's the one kind of boat that can never ever sink?
哪一种  友谊之船
What kind?  A friend ship!
哇  你真让我大开眼界
Wow! You blow my mind!
我要走了
I gotta go.
我该给你多少呢  二十块
How much do I owe you?  Twenty bucks.
这真是史上最便宜的大学了
It's like the cheapest college ever!